<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>How to on Karabiner-Elements</title>
    <link>/docs/help/how-to/</link>
    <description>Recent content in How to on Karabiner-Elements</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="/docs/help/how-to/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to change mouse buttons</title>
      <link>/docs/help/how-to/mouse-button/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs/help/how-to/mouse-button/</guid>
      <description>Karabiner-Elements does not modify mouse devices by default.&#xA;You have to enable your mouse on Karabiner-Elements Settings &amp;gt; Devices. Then, use Simple Modifications to assign a key to a button or use Complex Modifications for more advanced usage. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to use sticky modifier keys</title>
      <link>/docs/help/how-to/sticky-modifier-key/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs/help/how-to/sticky-modifier-key/</guid>
      <description>You can enable the sticky modifier keys from Karabiner-Elements Settings &amp;gt; Simple modifications.&#xA;Note The sticky modifier keys acts as general modifier key while you are pressing and holding down the key.&#xA;For example, the following operation result is AA instead of Aa.&#xA;Press sticky left shift key Press a key Release a key Press a key Release a key Release sticky left shift key If you want to disable this feature, use sticky modifier key (pressing and holding down is disabled).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to disable caps lock delay</title>
      <link>/docs/help/how-to/disable-caps-lock-delay/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs/help/how-to/disable-caps-lock-delay/</guid>
      <description>Karabiner-Elements disables the caps lock delay without any action since v13.3.0.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is it possible to adjust the key repeat rate?</title>
      <link>/docs/help/how-to/key-repeat/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs/help/how-to/key-repeat/</guid>
      <description>Karabiner-Elements does not provide a feature to adjust key repeat rate.&#xA;Use System Settings &amp;gt; Keyboard.&#xA;You can also adjust the key repeat rate using defaults write command. https://apple.stackexchange.com/questions/10467/how-to-increase-keyboard-key-repeat-rate-on-os-x</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to disable running Karabiner-Elements at login</title>
      <link>/docs/help/how-to/disable-open-at-login/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs/help/how-to/disable-open-at-login/</guid>
      <description>Karabiner-Elements will be started automatically at login after once you have run Karabiner-ELements.&#xA;Quit Karabiner-Elements if you want to stop running Karabiner-Elements at login.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
