<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Troubleshooting on Karabiner-Elements</title>
    <link>/docs/help/troubleshooting/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Troubleshooting on Karabiner-Elements</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="/docs/help/troubleshooting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Driver alert keeps showing up</title>
      <link>/docs/help/troubleshooting/driver-alert-keeps-showing-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs/help/troubleshooting/driver-alert-keeps-showing-up/</guid>
      <description>Usually, the following driver alert will appear on first start-up and the alert will disappear after you allow the system software from System Settings.&#xA;Unfortunately, the allow button may sometimes not appear in System Settings due to a problem with macOS driver loading.&#xA;In this case, you can display the allow button by deactivating and activating driver as described in the Advanced section on the alert.&#xA;macOS Catalina Notes Karabiner-Elements requires macOS 10.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Allow button in Privacy &amp; Security System Settings does not appear</title>
      <link>/docs/help/troubleshooting/allow-button-does-not-appear/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs/help/troubleshooting/allow-button-does-not-appear/</guid>
      <description>The allow button in Privacy &amp;amp; Security System Settings appear for your approval after you open Karabiner-Elements for the first time.&#xA;However, this allow button may not appear in some environments.&#xA;Reason The exact cause of the issue has not been determined, but it may be caused by the corrupted system cache by a macOS issue.&#xA;This issue may be resolved by starting macOS in safe mode to refresh the system cache.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Allow button in Privacy &amp; Security System Settings does not work</title>
      <link>/docs/help/troubleshooting/allow-button-does-not-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs/help/troubleshooting/allow-button-does-not-work/</guid>
      <description>The allow button in Privacy &amp;amp; Security System Settings should be hidden after you click it. If the button does not hide after click, you did not succeed to click it.&#xA;Reason The exact cause of the issue has not been determined, but it may be caused by the corrupted system cache by a macOS issue.&#xA;This issue may be resolved by starting macOS in safe mode to refresh the system cache.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#34;Fumihiko Takayama&#34; is shown in Login Items</title>
      <link>/docs/help/troubleshooting/fumihiko-takayama-in-login-items/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs/help/troubleshooting/fumihiko-takayama-in-login-items/</guid>
      <description>In Allow in the Background of Login Items, Fumihiko Takayama may appear instead of Karabiner-Elements.&#xA;There are several causes, but the problem is mainly on the macOS side and is difficult to resolve. (Restarting macOS may solve this issue)&#xA;In any case, there is no problem with leaving it as it is.&#xA;Expected:&#xA;Information for those who want to know more The confirmed causes are as follows:&#xA;If you have ever git clone the Karabiner-Elements repository and built it If macOS has set the Allow in the Background display name before Karabiner-Elements was registered in the macOS application database How to solve when you have built Karabiner-Elements from source code The Login Items referes Launch Services database to determine the display name.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Karabiner-Elements stopped working after macOS update</title>
      <link>/docs/help/troubleshooting/stopped-working-after-macos-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs/help/troubleshooting/stopped-working-after-macos-update/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s an issue of macOS that macOS update sometimes does not restore the running process state sufficiently after macOS update.&#xA;Please follow the instruction to solve the problem.&#xA;Restart macOS once again after macOS update. Reinstall Karabiner-Elements if restart macOS does not solve the problem. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Touch Bar does not change to f1-f12 when I press the fn key</title>
      <link>/docs/help/troubleshooting/touch-bar-function-keys/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs/help/troubleshooting/touch-bar-function-keys/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s an issue of macOS, and unfortunately, Karabiner-Elements cannot avoid this issue.&#xA;Instead, please change fn+number keys to function keys in Karabiner-Elements configuration.&#xA;Import Map fn + number keys to function keys Enable Map fn + number keys to their corresponding function keys. You can use f1-f12 keys by fn+number keys. Note If you are using &amp;ldquo;Use all F1, F2, etc. keys as standard function keys.&amp;rdquo;, enable Map fn + number keys to their corresponding media control keys instead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Control-eject shortcut does not work when Karabiner-Elements is running</title>
      <link>/docs/help/troubleshooting/control-eject/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs/help/troubleshooting/control-eject/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s an issue of macOS, and unfortunately, Karabiner-Elements cannot avoid this issue.&#xA;Instead, please change fn+escape to eject and use control+fn+escape (== control+eject) shortcut.&#xA;Import Change escape key. Enable Change fn+escape to eject.&#xA;You can use control+fn+escape as control+eject. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cannot use some three key combinations (key event is not fired)</title>
      <link>/docs/help/troubleshooting/cannot-use-some-key-combination/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs/help/troubleshooting/cannot-use-some-key-combination/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s a hardware limitation of your keyboard called &amp;ldquo;two-key rollover&amp;rdquo; if you cannot use some three key combinations. (e.g., physical left command key + right command key + m)&#xA;There are two way to avoid the rollover problem.&#xA;Use another keyboard which is N-key rollover. Use other key combinations. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#34;karabiner.json is not owned by a valid user&#34; error message in log</title>
      <link>/docs/help/troubleshooting/json-owner-is-invalid/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs/help/troubleshooting/json-owner-is-invalid/</guid>
      <description>If the following error message is appeared in log, your home directory owner ship is not valid.&#xA;[warning] [grabber] /Users/.../karabiner.json is not owned by a valid user. The cause is that you are using an external storage and locating your home directory into the volume.&#xA;You have to enable ownership on the external volume by the following command in Terminal.app.&#xA;sudo diskutil enableOwnership disk99999s99999 (Replace disk99999s99999 with your disk identifier which you can find by diskutil list command.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Placeholder Developer is shown in Security &amp; Privacy System Preferences</title>
      <link>/docs/help/troubleshooting/placeholder-developer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs/help/troubleshooting/placeholder-developer/</guid>
      <description>Note This page is for macOS 10.15 Catalina, not macOS 11 Big Sur or later. &amp;ldquo;.Karabiner-VirtualHIDDevice-Manager&amp;rdquo; is usually shown in Security &amp;amp; Privacy System Preferences when macOS requires your approval.&#xA;However, &amp;ldquo;Placeholder Developer&amp;rdquo; will be shown due to a macOS issue if you meet all of the following criteria:&#xA;You are using macOS Catalina (10.15) Multiple system software are waiting your approval. Workarounds In this case, you can choose one of the following three options to use Karabiner-Elements:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caps Lock LED not working</title>
      <link>/docs/help/troubleshooting/caps-lock-led-not-working/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs/help/troubleshooting/caps-lock-led-not-working/</guid>
      <description>Karabiner-Elements has a setting to disable caps lock LED control.&#xA;If your caps lock LED is not working properly, this setting may be enabled, so check the Manipulate caps lock LED setting in the Devices tab.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Settings window is shown at login</title>
      <link>/docs/help/troubleshooting/preferences-window-shown-at-login/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs/help/troubleshooting/preferences-window-shown-at-login/</guid>
      <description>If you manually registered Karabiner-Elements to Open at Login, the settings window will always appear at startup.&#xA;Karabiner-Elements will start automatically via launchd even if it is not in Open at Login, so remove it from your Open at Login.&#xA;Open System Settings. Open General &amp;gt; Login Items. Remove Karabiner-Elements from Open at Login. Caution Do not disable Karabiner-Elements.app in Allow in the Background. It&amp;rsquo;s a required setting for Karabiner-Elements to work.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Input symbols are different from the key code name on non-ANSI keyboards</title>
      <link>/docs/help/troubleshooting/symbols-with-non-ansi-keyboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs/help/troubleshooting/symbols-with-non-ansi-keyboard/</guid>
      <description>This is the intended behavior.&#xA;The key code name using in Karabiner-Elements is HID usage name. This is close to the physical key location on the ANSI layout keyboard.&#xA;For this reason, there are mismatches of symbols actually input and key code names on non-ANSI keyboards.&#xA;Determining which characters are to be input by keyboard event is the later step in the processing flow of macOS. Karabiner-Elements changes input events on a layer closer to the hardware, which is why it works like this.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compatibility with Logitech Logi Options&#43;: Fn keys</title>
      <link>/docs/help/troubleshooting/logitech-logi-options-plus-compatibility/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs/help/troubleshooting/logitech-logi-options-plus-compatibility/</guid>
      <description>This was discovered when using an MX Keys keyboard with the “Logi Options+” software. While Karabiner Elements is running, the Logitech specific function keys (such as Fn-esc to toggle between function keys and media keys and f1, f2, f3 to switch between inputs) are not recognized.&#xA;The solution is to edit karabiner.json such that the &amp;quot;fn_function_keys&amp;quot; array is empty:&#xA;&amp;#34;fn_function_keys&amp;#34;: [] Credit: https://github.com/pqrs-org/Karabiner-Elements/issues/1450#issuecomment-1013932206</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
