<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Getting started on Karabiner-Elements</title>
    <link>/docs/getting-started/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Getting started on Karabiner-Elements</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="/docs/getting-started/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Installation</title>
      <link>/docs/getting-started/installation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs/getting-started/installation/</guid>
      <description>Some operations are required to grant proper permission from macOS to Karabiner-Elements. Follow these instructions to set up Karabiner-Elements.&#xA;Install Karabiner-Elements Open the downloaded file. Open the .pkg file. The installer will be opened. Install Karabiner-Elements. After installation, you&amp;rsquo;ll need to grant the necessary permissions for Karabiner-Elements to function. This is part of macOS&amp;rsquo;s protection mechanism to prevent applications from accessing information without user consent. There are a few required steps, so please follow the instructions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Features</title>
      <link>/docs/getting-started/features/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs/getting-started/features/</guid>
      <description>Karabiner-Elements is a powerful and stable keyboard customizer for macOS.&#xA;Core features Simple Modifications: Change normal keys to other keys. Complex Modifications: Change keys by complex rules. Change a key to combination of modifiers. (e.g. change capslock to control+command) Change modifiers+key to key. (e.g. change control+m to return) Send key events if a key is pressed alone. Send key events if keys are pressed simultaneously. Mouse keys. etc. Function Keys: Change f1-f12 keys to media controls.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
