<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Documentation on Karabiner-Elements</title>
    <link>/docs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Documentation on Karabiner-Elements</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Privacy</title>
      <link>/docs/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs/privacy/</guid>
      <description>Privacy Security and privacy protection is one of the most important points of Karabiner-Elements architecture design.&#xA;Of course, Karabiner-Elements does not collect any of your input data, your configuration data, nor your usage statistics.&#xA;Data not collected Karabiner-Elements does not transmit your data externally. The following data is never transmitted outside your Mac:&#xA;Your keystrokes Your configuration data Your usage statistics And all other data except Karabiner-Elements version information. About Input Monitoring Karabiner-Elements exclusively receives input events from your keyboard, and then modifies them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/docs/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs/contact/</guid>
      <description>Reporting Bugs, Feature requests Please post an issue to GitHub.&#xA;Karabiner-Elements KE-complex_modifications (About complex modifications) Required information with bug reports Please fill your information when you send bug reports:&#xA;Required information macOS version: Karabiner version:&#xA;(You can confirm the version in &amp;ldquo;Update&amp;rdquo; tab in Karabiner Settings.) Your Mac hardware: Your keyboard hardware: Example:&#xA;macOS version: macOS 14.1.2 Karabiner version: Karabiner-Elements 14.13.0 Your Mac hardware: M2 MacBook Air Your keyboard hardware: Das Keyboard 4 Professional for Mac Mechanical Keyboard Other Send a message to author of Karabiner-Elements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pricing</title>
      <link>/docs/pricing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs/pricing/</guid>
      <description>Karabiner-Elements is an open source software and you can use it without any purchases.&#xA;Supporting this project This project accepts your funding via GitHub Sponsors or PayPal.&#xA;For donors I appreciate all donors. I received your donations!&#xA;I&amp;rsquo;m afraid I don&amp;rsquo;t have enough time to reply for donors.&#xA;(I&amp;rsquo;m giving priority to develop Karabiner-Elements at the moment.)&#xA;Dec 17, 2023&#xA;Takayama Fumihiko Monthly or One-time (GitHub Sponsors) Takayama Fumihiko @tekezo Open GitHub Sponsors page One-time (PayPal) Open PayPal Payments Form (Pay $10 for Karabiner-Elements) Note: This is effectively a donation but it has taken the form of software fee because of Japanese law and the constraints on government regulation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Release notes</title>
      <link>/docs/releasenotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs/releasenotes/</guid>
      <description>Karabiner-Elements 14.13.0 📦 Download 📅 Release date Dec 9, 2023 🔔 Important Notes A reboot is required when upgrading from version 14.12.0 or earlier, to update the virtual keyboard driver. ✨ New Features Palm detection is supported in MultitouchExtension. (Thanks to @quarkw) Use Bluetooth address (Bluetooth MAC address) is used to identify the device when the Bluetooth device does not have Vendor ID and Product ID. (Thanks to @stackia) Add the following settings into Devices tab.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
